Aslan Abdygaliyev Junior Frontend Developer

xabda001@gmail.com | +77775158206 | Astana

https://www.linkedin.com/in/аслан-абдыгалиев-7a1254220 | https://github.com/AslanAb

I have successfully graduated from the 'IT STEP' Computer Academy with a focus on Front-end development.

Throughout my studies, I gained expertise in HTML, CSS, JS, and explored frameworks/libraries such as Node (back-end), Vue, React, and Angular. My emphasis was on the React library, and I utilized the Next.js framework to develop my diploma project.

During my learning journey, I took the initiative to independently seek information and solve complex problems. While I have made significant progress, I recognize the value of having an experienced mentor to accelerate my path towards becoming a senior web developer.

Skills

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

TypeScript

Node js

React js

React Native

Vue js

Education

Junior Frontend Developer Computer Academy "IT STEP" 2022 - 2023

Languages

English - Intermediate

Russian - Fluent

Kazakh - Fluent

Experience

Lowyer | Institute of World Economics and Politics 2022 - 2023 | Astana

Lowyer | 'Samgau' Holding 2019 - 2022 | Astana

Mathematic teacher | School of Education 'Pythagoras' 2018 - 2019 | Astana

Pet-projects

Next js, Tailwind, React Transition Group

https://github.com/AslanAb/kazhmuratov_bureau_web_v_0_1.git

JavaScript

https://github.com/AslanAb/project_js_exam.git

Node js

https://github.com/AslanAb/node_js_exam_project.git

Vue is

https://github.com/AslanAb/vue_js_project_exam.git

React is

https://github.com/AslanAb/react_exam_project.git https://github.com/AslanAb/star_wars.git